翻译：CS小明漫画家  胡好时  foxer  鱼骨头
校对：原子蛋    总监   原子蛋
后期：加森     时间轴：sagelibra  今
南方公园  第十七季第八集
屁与火之歌
《南方公园》
前情回顾
我们马上就要展开
Soon we'll be fighting
一场有生以来最惨烈的战斗  黑色星期五
the greatest battle of our young hard lives. Black Friday.
黑色星期五  11月29日  南方公园购物中心
想要PS4的人  加入我们这边
Everyone who wants to get PS4s, join with us.
南方公园商场的汤姆说他们已经加强保安戒备
Tom, the south park mall says, they've beefed up security
你对其他男人
You have a strong influence over
影响甚大  麦考密克夫人
the rest of the men, Lady McKormick.
你不能死
You can't die.
我们觉得你该看看这个
We thought you should see this.
凛冬将至  选好队伍  (要Xbox1  不要PS4)
《权力的游戏》中会怎么做
What would they do on Game of Thrones?
事情到了最黑暗的境地  他们会怎么做
What would they do when things look their darkest?
让我来告诉你  孩子  战争就要到来了
Well, let me tell you child of a war that is about to come.
从被忘却的时代起  他们双方就都存在了
Since time unremembered there has been two.
一个是黑暗而不可原谅的
One dark and unforgiving.
另一个是纯洁而充满光明的
The other pure and filled with light.
战争的黎明  我独自站着
At the dawn of war I stand alone
留意着哪里会是最后的战场
looking out at what will be the last battlefield
因为凛冬即将到来  而我就是公主殿下
for winter is coming and I am a princess.
曾经是黑暗大军的普通女子
Once a common lady of the dark army
而今晚  一场仪式使我重生为公主
but tonight my rite equaled princess by birth
我背叛了大家
I betrayed my kind.
未来就在此处  预订你的新一代机型
并选择了我的队伍
And now I have chosen my side
我相信  自己的选择是最好的
that which I believe is best for all
它拥有带扬声器的双振动手柄
what has a dual shock controller with a speaker
接触面更有触摸板
and touch pad interface.
我的祖国一分为二
Our land is split in two.
兄弟反目
Brother against brother.
友人成仇
Friend versus friend.
我的双亲也要为黑色星期五而战
My parents will fight on black Friday as well
目的却无从知晓
for what I do not know.
他穿了什么鬼东西
What the hell is he wearing now?
我的追随者甚少
My followers they are few in number,
而他们将帮我识破一切
shall help see me through
直到我的公主身份被天下人接受
until I'm finally accepted as a princess by all.
我不能懈怠  因为我知道  即使现在
I cannot rest for I know that even now
仇敌也在为战争而操练
the enemy is training for battle,
也在为凛冬而准备
also preparing for winter.
好了  停  停  停
All right. Stop, stop, stop.
仗不是这么打的
This is not how you fight.
你们以为是儿戏吗
You think this is a joke?
黑色星期五那天  会有
On black Friday there is gonna be
成千的采购者想闯进购物中心
thousands of shoppers trying to get in that mall
让你很难买到Xbox1
keeping you from getting an Xbox1s.
我们该怎么做
So what do we do?
我们要了解敌情
We survey each enemy
然后攻其软肋
and we attack their weak spot.
斯考特・梅尔・金森有糖尿病
Scott Mal Kinson has diabetes
所以我们攻其软肋
so we hit him in his weak shot.
-妈呀  -另一支军队自认为比我们强
- Oh god. - There is another army out there who think they're better than us.
我们才不会被叛徒贱人肯尼打败呢
And we're not going to be beat by the traitor whore Kenny.
继续操练
Get back to training.
卡特曼  我们也许该谈谈胜算问题
Cartman, we should probably talk about our chances.
他们都缺乏经验凯尔
The men are just inexperienced Kyle.
他们需要多多操练
They need more training.
这还不够
It's not enough.
自从肯尼改了队伍
Ever since Kenny switched sides,
很多人都想在黑色星期五去抢购PS4了
there are more kids that want to go with the PS4 on black Friday.
那个该死的叛徒
That god damn traitor,
肯尼这么做你也不开心  对吧
you don't like Kenny doing this, right?
因为他想当公主  而我要阻止他
Because he wanted to be a princess and I wouldn't let him.
我跟他说过  你可以当小妞
I said, you can be a chick Kenny,
但统治者只有一个  那就是我
but there is only one ruler, and that's me!
索尼公司发布PS4了  卡特曼
Sony released the PS4s, Cartman,
他们接受采访了
they are being reviewed.
大家越来越喜欢PS4了
People are liking them.
我敢打赌  索尼发售的这个黑星期五套装
I guarantee you Kenny had something to do with Sony
跟肯尼脱不了干系
offering  a black Friday bundle deal.
去操练他们吧  凯尔
Just keep them in trainings Kyle.
肯尼这个暗箭伤人的游戏  两人玩儿就够了
Two can play Kenny's back-stabbing game.
傻逼混蛋
Stupid ass hole.
卡萨・伯尼塔餐厅  [第七季  第11集]
喂你好  请找Xbox的董事长
Yes, hello, I'd like to speak to the President of Xbox, please.
Xbox的董事长  就是Xbox的头儿
the President of Xbox, like the head of Xbox.
好吧  微软CEO
Fine, CEO, Microsoft,
随便叫啥  让他接电话
whatever, put him on.
我要人帮我一网打尽PS的人
I need help uploading PlayStation people.
我叫埃里克・卡特曼  我是巫师和国王
I'm Eric Cartman a wizard and a king.
巫师国王  对
A wizard king, yes.
不  不是巫师国国王
No, not a king of wizards.
我是国王  又恰好是个巫师
I'm a king that happened to be a wizard.
赶紧让微软CEO接电话吧
Just put the CEO of Microsoft on the phone.
鲍尔默先生  市场部的约翰和戴夫想见你
Mr. Balmer, John and Dave from marketing are here to see you.
好吧  你们好  什么情况
Yes, hello. How are things going out there?
执行官  战争的趋势正在改变
Sir, the tides of war're changing.
科罗拉多有位国王
There's a king in Colorado.
这位年轻的巫师确信
A young wizard who believes that
如果我们不帮他  索尼就会棋高一招了
Sony will have the upper hand if we do not come to his aid.
他声称  通过我们的帮助
He claims that with our help
他的部众就能更好地准备
his followers are prepared to
为"哪家系统更强大"而誓死战斗
fight to the death for which system is better.
我不懂你们在说什么
What are you guys talking about?
听起来很荒谬
You sound ridiculous.
黑色星期五  在一座小镇
There's going to be a war in the small town
会爆发战争  新闻都在报呢
on black Friday and it's all over the news.
伙计们  只是机型之战
Guys, these are console wars.
又不是什么王国的宏伟战争  拜托
Not some epic battle for a kingdom, I mean come on.
但是  这孩子说他是巫师
But this one kid says he's a wizard
而且索尼公司正在...
and that Sony is helping...
伙计们  只不过是游戏机罢了  好吗
Guys, guys, it's just a video game machine. Alright?
我们微软是要
Microsoft's a company that
努力成为盈利最多的公司  好吗
tries to be above all the pelty commercialism, okay?
-好吧  -好  好吧
- Okay. - O-Okay.
离黑色星期五还有几天时间
Well, black Friday is still a few days away
但它好像已经宣布了另一种灾难
but it looks like it's already claimed another fatality.
尼尔斯・劳森正在现场
Niles Lawson is on the scene.
尼尔斯  你那有什么消息
Niles what are you hearing?
很不幸  昨晚汤姆被袭击的同时
Tom tragedy struck last night
购物中心保安警官迈尔斯・哈皮・达维斯
when a mall security officer Miles Happy Davis was beat to death
被这根糖果拐杖活活打死
with this candy cane.
就因为他对一位母亲说
After telling a mother
周四晚上之前都不能开始排队
she couldn't line up for black Friday until Thursday night.
为表示对这位牺牲的保安的敬意
In honor of the slaying mall's seurity officer,
购物中心正式决定
the mall has decided to
黑色星期五的交易额外降价10%
officially drop another 10% off black Friday deals.
黑色星期五  荣誉墙  1974年建立
哈皮是个好人
Happy was a good man.
他太好了  不该以这种
Too good to have died in such a
残酷又欢乐的方式死去
brutal but festive manner.
队长  队长
Captain, captain,
购物中心为黑色星期五又降价了10%
the mall is dropping the black Friday sale another 10%.
-什么  -偶滴神啊
- What? - Oh, my god.
那就是打一折了
That's 90% off.
天呐  他们回来了
Oh, god, they're back.
购物者们回来啦
The shoppers are back.
大家原地待命
Everybody stay put.
我来解决
I'll handle this.
若你们是为了黑色星期五而来
If you are here for black Friday
那在感恩节午夜之前不准进入商场范围
you cannot be on mall property until midnight on Thanksgiving.
我们还没进入商场范围呢
We' in the on mall property.
但是你们马上就要了
Well, you're about to be.
那我们要是走得特别特别慢呢
Well, what if we just walk really, really slow.
黑色星期五
Black Friday.
你们得走得再慢一些
You gonna have to walk slower than that.
还很有点时间呢
You get a while.
我们可以走得非常慢的  瞧
We can walk really slow, look.
自作聪明
Smart asses.
巴特斯圣骑士
Paladin Butters,
我正想要和你谈谈麦考密克夫人
I was hoping I could talk to you about Lady McKormick.
您是指肯尼公主吗  大人
You mean Princess Kenny, my lord?
是的  随便啦
Yeah, whatever.
那个小鸡巴以为自己是丹妮莉丝・坦格利安
That little prick thinks he's Daenerys Targaryen.
我要知道如何才能解决掉他
I need to know how do they deal with him?
在《权力的游戏》里
How did they deal with
他们是怎么解决龙族女王的
the queen of dragons in Game of Thrones?
他们没有
They don't!
什么  你有没有照我说的看完第三季
Well, did you finish watching Season 3 like I asked you?
我看完了
Yeah, I have finished it.
那么龙出现时发生了什么
So, what happens when the dragons show up?
什么都没发生
Nothing!
龙还在路上呢
The dragons are still on their way.
他们不停说会有龙
They keep promising dragons
但我只看到软趴趴的鸡鸡
but all I get are more floppy wieners in my face.
巴特斯  胜利的关键
BUtters, the key to our victory
就是要紧随《权力的游戏》的剧情
is following the Game of Thrones model exactly.
我要知道龙出现后发生了什么
I have to know what happens when dragons show up,
这样我就知道怎么解决肯尼了
so I know how to deal with Kenny.
那你要我怎样呢
What do you want me to do?
这里有两张去新墨西哥州的车票
Here's two bus tickets to New Mexico.
我要你带上斯科特・ 马尔金森爵士
I want you to take Sir Scott Malkinson,
然后找乔治・马丁问到答案
and go seek out George R. R. Martin for answers.
乔治・马丁是谁
Who is George R. R. Martin?
巴特斯  他就是《权力的游戏》的作者
He's the guy who write Game of Thrones, Butters.
他可以告诉我们要如何解决掉肯尼
He can let us both know how to handle Kenny
还有我们是否该出卖克莱德
and if we should betray Clyde or not.
面对现实吧  巴特斯
Let's face it, Butters.
这其实就只关于你和我得到Xbox
This is really about you and me getting Xboxes.
其他人的存在只是为了
The rest are simply there
帮我们进入那几扇门罢了
to help us get through the doors.
我说了让你们滚出我家后院的
I told you kids to stay out of my damn yard.
回避下好吗  我们正说话呢
Do you mind? We're trying to talk here.
为什么每次你和别人说话
Yeah? Well how come every time you talk to somebody
都是在讲出卖另一个人的事
it's about betraying somebody else.
要你多管闲事
Why don't you mind your own business.
最后听好了
No, listen for the last time
我们无龙可派
we don't have any dragons to send them.
要是有人想要PS  那是他们的选择
If some people want to choose Playstations it's their choice.
先生  盖茨先生来了
Sir, Mr. Gates is here.
比尔・盖茨吗
Bill Gates?
我得挂了
I got to go.
比尔・盖茨居然到公司来了
Hey, Bill Gates actually showing up at corporate.
史蒂夫  最近如何
Hey Steve, how you doing?
不错
Not bad.
正要处理些媒体的事情
You know, just trying to get the next gen press stuff handled.
我听说在科罗拉多州某地出了点小状况
I heard there's a little trouble in Colorado some where?
没有  没什么大事
Oh, it's not. Turns out it was nothing.
就是一帮小屁孩
Just some kids're trying to
想把主机之争弄得更大
turn the console wars into something bigger.
我的天呐
Oh, my gosh.
史蒂夫  你知道当我退下来
You know when I stepped down
并决定让你负责公司时
and left you in charge of the company Steve,
我知道可能对你来说是个挑战
I knew there might be some challenges for you.
没有什么我解决不了的
Well, yeah. Nothing I can't handle.
我们可能需要改变营销策略
There may be some changes we need to make to our marketing,
但我还是很乐观的
but I'm optimistic.
我想我们最终可以达到预计的销量的
I think we will ultimately sell the number of units we want to.
没错  史蒂夫  是需要做出些改变了
You're right, Steve. Some changes do need to be made.
你知道弱点是什么吗  史蒂夫
Do you know what weakness is, Steve?
那就是相信竞争是良性的
Weakness is believes competion is healthy.
曾经Xbox和PS确实
See, there was a time when Xboxes and Playstations
可以共存
can both servive in this world.
但那段时光结束了
But that time is done.
现在的趋势是
It's all headed to one device
人们在同一平台上游戏  看电视和社交
that people game on, watch TV on, socialise on.
只会有一个胜利者
There's only going to be one winner.
我不能让你们这帮蠢货
I can't have you idiots throwing away
毁了我千辛万苦才得来的一切
everything I worked so hard to achieve.
把他处理掉
Clean that shit up.
快点  斯科特  你太慢了
Come on, Scott, you're lagging.
我觉得我的胰岛素偏低  我得吃东西
I think my insulin is low, I need to eat.
那我们就赶紧干完正事儿了去麦当劳
Let's just talk to this guy and then we can hit an McDonalds.
到了  2217
Here we go, 2217.
你们找谁
Can I help you?
你好
Hello?
这里是乔治・ 马丁家吗
Is this George R. R. Martin's house?
请问你们是谁
Who is this, please?
两个想知道
Two kids that want to know
龙出现后的剧情的小孩
what happens when the dragons show up?
在吗
Hello?
对不起  但是马丁先生不见粉丝
I'm sorry but Mr. Martin does not see fans.
我们不是粉丝
We're not fans.
我们根本不喜欢
Yeah. We don't like it.
根本就不喜欢
We don't like it.
而且说实话我非常讨厌这部剧
And I'm pretty pissed off if you want to know the truth.
为什么
About what?
让我进去见乔治・马丁  我再告诉他
Let me talk to George R. R. Martin and I'll tell him about what.
都怪血色婚礼  是吧
It's the red wedding, isn't it?
你们是恨我把所有人都杀了吧
You hate how I killed everyone off?
不是  我们只是要了解龙的剧情
No, sir. We just really need to know about the dragons
但是它们根本没出现
but they never seem to show up.
它们会来的
They're coming.
龙已经在路上了
The dragons are on their way.
啥时候到
When?
你们真的想知道吗
You really want to know?
求你了  很着急
Please. It's urgent.
好吧
All right.
乔佛里国王仍在君临城
King Joffrey is still in king's landing.
但有一个年轻的铁匠
But there's a young black smith
一天早上起来想到了一个主意
who wakes up one morning with a plan,
他的鸡鸡软软地挂在两腿之间
and his wiener gently hangs down between his legs.
他软趴趴的鸡鸡在晨光中熠熠生辉
Soft and flaccid, his wiener glistened in the golden sun slight.
停  能不能跳过鸡鸡的部分直接说龙
No. Can we skip the wiener stuff and get to the dragons?
糟糕  我觉得我要晕了
Oh shit. I think I'm going faint.
怎么了  斯科特
What's the matter, Scott?
我说了我每两个小时就得吃东西
I told you I have to eat every two hours.
他有糖尿病
He's diabetic.
天啊  你
Oh gee. You--
孩子们进来暖和下吧
Why don't you kids come out the cold?
我来定披萨
I will order some pizzas.
噢  好  谢谢
Oh, ok. Thanks.
进来吧
Come on in and I'll tell you
我会告诉你们《权力的游戏》后面的剧情
everything that gonna happen in Game of Thrones.
凯尔爵士  我想跟你聊聊斯坦
Sir Kyle I wanted to talk to you about Stan.
卡特曼  如果你是想确定我不会叛变
If you want to make sure I'm not switching sides, Cartman,
就没什么好担心的了
you don't have to worry.
斯坦错了
Stan is wrong.
不是这事
It isn't that.
肯尼公主深受她军队的爱戴
Princess Kenny is loved by her army
而斯坦却疯狂追随她的指挥
but Stan is still nuts as balls of her operation.
一事就可阻碍叛徒们得到PS
It would be a huge set back to the trators getting their Play Stations
就是让斯坦被禁足
if Stan were to be grounded.
因为什么被禁足
Gounded for what?
那就看你的了
That could be up to you.
不  你说过没人会被禁足
No. Cartman, you said nobody would have to be grounded.
我们不玩阴的
We're not playing dirty.
那好吧  凯尔爵士
Fine, Sir Kyle.
也许你是对的
Perhaps you're right.
你知道斯坦他爸在商场安保兼职吗
Did you know that Stan's dad is working a temp job at mall security
什么
What?
看起来还挺方便  不是么
It seems a little convenient, doesn't it?
斯坦有内线可以帮他搞到PS4
Stan will have somebody inside to help him get PS4s.
现在又是谁玩阴的了
Who's playing dirty now?
直说吧  凯尔爵士
Let's face it, Sir Kyle.
这只关乎于你和我得到Xbox
This is all about you and me getting Xboxes.
其他人都只是我们的垫脚石而已
The rest are simply there to help us get through those doors.
别信他
Don't believe it.
他跟一堆人这么说过了
He said that to a bunch of people.
哥们  你再骚扰我就报警啦
Dude, you better stop harassing me or I'm calling the cops.
你报警
You're calling the cops?
-是  -你私闯民宅我才要报警
- Yeah. - You're on my property. I'm calling the cops.
那你他妈倒是报啊
Then call the fucking cops then.
2012年日间新闻最佳奖
噢  是你啊
Oh, it's you.
汤姆  我站在你家走廊上是因为
Tom, I'm standing in your doorway
我们有个大新闻要报道
because we have a hot news story to report.
我们还有一小时才开工呢
We don't go to work for another hour.
我们才接到比尔・盖茨的来电
We just got a call from Bill Gates.
他保证黑色星期五能掀起大战
He says he can promise us a bigger war on Black Friday
只要我们合作的话
if we play along.
他想拉拢我们吗
He wants us to side with him?
没错  塔米
That's right, Tammy.
别忘了
Let's not forget having
黑色星期五的血战会是超好的题材
a blood bath on Black Friday is good for the news.
是有益于我们的
It's good for us.
越严重越好
The bigger the better.
我们旨在播报新闻而不是让它更暴力
Our job is to report the news not make it more violent?
真对  汤姆  你这人太正直了
Right, Tom, because you're so about integrity.
快走
Let's go.
也许我应该跟新闻间里的
Maybe I should let everyone in
所有人说他们的两位主播在干嘛
the news room know what their two anchors are up to.
没的说了吧
Back to you.
9频道早间新闻
由汤姆和塔米・汤普森主持
现在由科罗拉多最热兄妹主播
It's the morning news with Tom and Tammy Thompson.
汤姆和塔米汤普森为您播报早间新闻
Colorado's top-rated brother-sister news team.
黑色星期五就要到来
Well, Black Friday is just around the corner, and
塔米  现在局面更加紧张了
Tammy, it's getting fierce out there.
没错
That's right.
奈尔斯・劳森正带着节日惊喜等在商场外
Niles Lawson is at the mall with a a little holiday surprise.
塔米  黑色星期五的热情已达到巅峰
Tammy, the excitement over Black Friday is peaking and
现在比尔・盖茨本人现身想助一臂之力
now Bill Gates himself has shown up to try to make it even bigger.
没错
That's right.
我们想要尽可能帮助我们的拥护者
We want to do whatever we can to help our supporters get
在周五拿到超值的Xbox折扣
their Xboxes at incredible deals on Friday,
所以我们提供了宝剑和战斧
so we've come to offer swords and battle axes,
所有轻便并能帮孩子们杀出条血路的武器
whatever the kids can carry to fight their way through other shoppers.
据悉你们还给孩子们捐赠了枪支
We understand you've donated some guns to the kids as well.
是的  但仅限拥护者人手一支
Yes, but we are limited one per Xbox follower
因为最重要的还是安全
because the key thing here on everyone's mind is safety.
找哪位
Yes?
肯尼在家吗
Hi, is Kenny home?
他在后院和朋友们玩呢
Yeah, Kenny's out back playing with his friends.
前进  勇士们
Forward, men.
这
That--um--
你们转一下
You guys turn me.
敌人来了
It's the enemy.
准  准  准备防御
Defense p--p--positions
出去
Get--
快点儿  滚出去
Come on. Get out.
我看到了护法们和麦考密克公主
I see guardians with the traitor Lady McKormick.
让他们过来
Let them pass.
公主欢迎大肥猪来访我国
The Princess bids your fat ass welcome
并要你呈上来访目的
to our kingdom and suggests you state your purpose.
你打不过这些人的
You can't win these guys.
看看周围
Look around you.
放下武器
Lay down your weapons and
回来与我们为Xbox而战吧
come back fight for Xboxes with us on Black Friday.
公主说如果你想改变主意
The Princess says that if you want to change
并承认PS更好  她就会考虑
your mind and agree that Play Stations are better she'll consider it.
肯尼  我们都有想扮小妞的时候
Kenny, we all understand wanting to play as a chick once in a while,
但你永远都不可能是真的公主
but you're never going to be a real Princess.
公主说你是舔蛋蛋的拉拉
The Princess calls you a ball-licking lesbian.
那压根都不合逻辑
That doesn't even make sense.
斯坦  这太过分了
Stan, this has gone too far.
人们会受到伤害的
People are going to get hurt.
你所发起的已经完全失控了
What you started is way out of control.
什么我发起的
What I started?
你怎么敢这么说
How dare you.
所有人都将会玩Xbox
All these people will be gaming on Xboxes.
你真想余生都只跟克雷格玩么
You really want to just game with Craig the rest of your life?
我宁愿跟克雷格玩
I'd rather game with Craig
也不想花一分钟建Xbox账号
than spend one minute having to set up a Xbox live account.
我们明天会得到PS的
We'll get our Play Stations tomorrow,
而你们这帮傻逼什么都得不到
and you buttholes will have nothing.
你们以寡敌众  而且也没时间了
You're outnumbered 10 to 1 and there's no time left.
怎么赢
How will you win?
神会指引我们的
The gods will find us a way.
然后山姆威尔・塔利看到军队来了
So, then Samwell Tarly sees the army approaching,
他的小鸡鸡大概有这么大
and his wiener is about this big.
他知道史坦尼斯・拜拉席恩的鸡鸡
He knows that Stannis Baratheon's weiner
可能已经冻小了
probably shrivel from the cold.
山姆威尔要召集勇士  怎么办呢
Samwell has to rally his men. So what does he do?
他拿出他的小鸡鸡
He takes out his wiener
然后在所有人面前晃来晃去
and he dangles it around for all his men to see.
先生  你刚才说披萨要到了
Sir, you said pizzas were coming.
对  对  在路上了
Yeah, yeah. They're on their way.
一会就到了
They're still coming.
于是山姆威尔的鸡鸡...
So Samwell's wiener goes--
可你说快到了说了三个小时了
But you said they were on their way like three hours ago.
披萨再不来我就倒地不起了
If I don't get pizza soon, I'm going to pass out.
别急  就快到了
Don't worry, they're coming.
披萨在路上了  会很好吃的
Pizzas are on their way and they're going to be amazing.
下面
Now,
琼恩・雪诺终于遇上了詹姆・兰尼斯特
Jon Snow finally faces Jaime Lannister,
这家伙的鸡鸡  超级大
And this guy's weiner is, you know, huge, right?
所以没那么简单
So it's not going to be easy.
盖茨先生  我想跟你谈谈星期五的大战
Mr. Gates, I was hoping I could talk to you about the fight tomorrow.
没问题  是埃里克吧
Certainly. Uh, Eric, right?
应该是巫师国王大人
It's my lord wizard king, actually.
你来作为领导人当然很有帮助
Having your leadership has certainly been a help,
但我希望我们讲清楚这是我的军队
but I hope that we're clear that this is my army.
王权只能掌握在一人手里
There can only be one person of royalty.
这是一种定数
That's kind of the ruse.
我当然不会侵犯你的权力
I certainly don't want to step on your toes.
别担心
Don't worry,
我很擅长让我的CEO做自己的决策
I'm quite good at letting my CEOs do what they want.
你的CEO
Your CEOs?
直说吧  只有我们两个可能拿到xbox
Let's face it-- this is really just about you and me getting xboxes.
其他人都是我们的垫脚石而已
The rest are simply there to help us get through those doors.
什么
What?
感觉如何呀
How's it feel?
现在谁是老大谁是小弟了
Now who's walking who through the betrayal garden?
你他妈就不能少管闲事吗
Why don't you stay the fuck out of my business?
你他妈就不能滚出我家院子吗
Why don't you stay the fuck out of my yard?
刚刚的啪啪让我欲仙欲死
That was amazing sex. I enjoyed it immensely.
不知你感觉如何
How about you?
[日语]
对于想在黑色星期五
You know, Microsoft has given kids
得到xbox的孩子们  微软给了很多帮助
who want xboxes on black Friday a lot of support.
战况如此一边倒似乎是一种耻辱
Seems a shame that the fight will be so one-sided.
[日语]
黑色星期五开战在即
Black Friday's about to happen,
很可能就没你什么事了
and it's not even going to be a fight.
这对我们两个都是坏消息
That's bad for both of us.
你一定有什么可以提供
There must be something you can give to kids
给喜欢索尼的孩子  让战争更加平衡
who want sonies to make the fight more even.
有
我有这个
是  我想这个可以见效
Yes, I think that will do nicely.
鸡鸡  鸡鸡鸡鸡  鸡鸡鸡鸡
Wiener. Wiener. Wiener. Wiener. Wiener. Wiener. Wiener.
两只鸡鸡傍地走
One wiener next to another wiener.
三只鸡鸡好朋友
Two wieners alongside yet another wiener.
鸡鸡大会
Wiener party.
软鸡鸡  松趴趴  不举鸡鸡
Soft wieners, nice and soft, non-erect wieners.
弹鸡鸡  甩鸡鸡
Flopping wieners. Dangling wieners.
五只鸡鸡上我脸
Five wieners in my face.
停  求别唱了
Stop! Stop, please.
我受不了了
I can't take any more.
可这是最精彩的部分
But this is the best part
就在乔佛里国王中毒之前
right before King Joffrey gets poisoned.
所有人的鸡鸡朝他脸上袭去
Everyone flips their wieners all around his face!
听着  老兄
Listen, buddy!
你说过披萨就在路上了
You promised that pizzas were on the way!
要是披萨还不来
If they don't show up right now,
你手下就会多一个孩子的亡魂
you're gonna have a dead kid on your hands.
听到没有
Do you hear me?
好好好  你们想吃什么披萨
Okay, fine, fine! What kind of pizzas do you want?
我们想吃什么
What kind do we want?
他都还没下单
He hasn't even ordered the pizzas yet!
别急  会有的
Don't worry, they're coming!
不只是两个披萨  会有...有五个
Not just two pizzas. There's-- there's gonna be five.
而且是至尊披萨  大得超乎你的想象
And they're gonna be huge! You won't believe it.
得了  斯科特  我们走
Come on, Scott. We're leaving.
等等  我还没告诉你剧情呢
Wait, I haven't told you what happens yet!
不用了  黑色星期五就要来了
No! Black Friday is about to happen,
我们要赶在第一批冲进商场
and my friends and I have to be the first ones inside the mall
去抢xbox
to get xboxes.
那你怎么不早说  这事我有办法
Well, why didn't you say so? I can help with that.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我来打几个电话
I'll make some calls.
我有办法让你们做好充足准备
I know a way to make sure you're completely prepared for black Friday.
索尼PS4
Sony ps4.
[日语]
索尼公司的总裁感谢你们对PS4的支持
The president of sony bids you thanks for all your support of the ps4.
[日语]
他送你这个礼物  让你永远成为
He offers you this gift to once and for all
真正的公主
make you an official princess
并赐予你力量
and to give you the powers you need
赢得黑色星期五之战的胜利
to win this war on black Friday.
[日语]
肯尼居然是日本公主
Wow, Kenny's a Japanese princess.
肯尼公主
天哪  我们完了
Oh, god, we're done for!
朋友们  时间就要到了
My friends, the time is almost here.
让我们拿出先我们而去的超市保安们
Let us face these shoppers with the bravery of
赋予我们的勇气  面对顾客们吧
those mall security officers before us.
马什司令
Commander Marsh.
他们什么
They're what?
他们要什么
They're going to what?
汤姆  我们从南方公园超市得到爆炸性新闻
Tom, we have breaking news from the South Park Mall,
为确保所有人都做好充分准备
in an effort to make sure everyone is prepared,
超市决定将黑色星期五延后一周
the mall has decided to push black Friday by one week.
什么
What?
黑色星期五  12月6日
这个天才的主意是乔治・马丁提出的
The genius idea was proposed by George R.R. Martin,
他同时提出了  "操他妈"
who also suggested: "Fuck it!
"我们来把感恩节推迟到12月3日"
Let's push Thanksgiving to December 3rd."
因为日期的推迟  超市决定将
For pushing the date, the mall is now reducing
黑色星期五的降价幅度调至96%
black Friday prices to 96% off
仅限前一百名进入超市的人
to the first 100 people inside the mall.
这里将化为血色的染缸  汤姆
This is going to be a fucking blood bath, Tom!
医疗帐篷  救护车  脸部彩绘将相继抵达
There will be medical tents, ambulances, face painting.
毫无疑问会有你熟悉和深爱的人丧命于此
No doubt a lot of people you know and love are going to die.